skyauction.com 2003-12-04

# SkyAuction.com Travel Auctions: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

SkyAuction.com has created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practice for the SkyAuction.com Web site (www.SkyAuction.com). Using the Internet should be a fun experience and we want to help you make it so.

When you reserve or purchase travel services through SkyAuction.com, we will ask you to provide us with personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, credit card information and other personal identifying information. We need this information in order to process your travel arrangements and need to share this personal information with the relevant airline, car rental agency, hotel, travel agency and/or other involved third party. Credit card information is not stored by the SkyAuction.com Web site. 

As a user of SkyAuction.com, you have the option to engage in certain additional activities on the site, such as entering contests or sweepstakes, or receiving our e-mail alerts. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, SkyAuction.com may require you to provide us with personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal identifying information. SkyAuction.com needs to collect this personal information for various reasons, which may include: (i) notifying sweepstake or contest winners, (ii) fulfilling prizes; (ii) disseminating our e-mail; (iii) aggregating statistical information; and (iv) tracking and verifying compliance with SkyAuction.com policies and international, federal, state and local laws. 

SkyAuction.com recognizes and respects the importance of responsible use of your personal information. If you do not want the information you provide to SkyAuction.com to be used to inform you of other products and special offers from SkyAuction.com, and you indicate this preference when you provide the information, SkyAuction.com will honor your preference. In case you change your mind or some personal information may change (such as your zip code), we provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you give us. You can do this at the member information page or by contacting our Customer Support organization. 

OPTING-OUT 

To keep you in control of your personal information and the communications directed to you, we allow you to opt-out of receiving certain communications from SkyAuction.com about new features or services. If a guest objects to such use for any reason, you may stop that use, either by e-mail request to SkyAuction Customer Support or by modifying your member information online. 

Information provided when reserving or purchasing travel services through SkyAuction.com, may be used for marketing and promotional purposes and is subject to the opt-out processes described on, or linked to, each order form. 

THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING 

We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.doubleclick.net/naiprivacy)

USE OF COOKIES 

Our Web site may use cookies to enhance your experience while using our Web site. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to the computer that is browsing that Web site for record keeping purposes. Use of cookies makes Web-surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your passwords and your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular Web site and making sure that you do not see the same ad repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard.

Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Web site will not function properly when you view them.

USE OF TRAFFIC DATA 

Each time a visitor comes to our Web site, we collect some information to improve the overall quality of the online experience. At the Web site, we collect the visitor's domain name (i.e., where the user is logged on, such as from Yahoo.com, etc.), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to the SkyAuction.com Web site), and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform). We collect visitor information for purposes of product monitoring, product improvement, and targeted advertising. We also count, track, and aggregate all visitors' activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the SkyAuction.com properties, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about you into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers; but SkyAuction.com will not disclose your individual identity or personal data without your permission. When SkyAuction.com does present aggregated information to outside companies, no one is able to identify you or contact you. 

USE OF IP ADDRESSES 

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, the big computers that 'serve up' web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. 

SkyAuction.com collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate, or combined, information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When users request pages from the SkyAuction.com Web site, our servers log the user's IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, customers or others. 

USE OF e-mail DATA 

SkyAuction.com will use your e-mail address to send correspondence about reservation confirmations, important updates about your travel plans and newsletters. Members who sign up to receive SkyAuction.com's newsletter and notifications of travel specials, will receive a SkyAuction.com content newsletter delivered either on a monthly basis, as well as occasional product-related announcements. 

Users can choose to unsubscribe from SkyAuction.com newsletters or product-related announcements at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions found in each e-mail or by contacting our Customer Support organization. 

CONTESTS AND SWEEPSTAKES 

SkyAuction.com offers contests and sweepstakes in which we request certain personal information. At a minimum, the required information includes name and e-mail address; in some cases, the user must answer survey questions about a range of other personal data. The information gathered in the entry form is used to verify the entrant's identity and to contact winners and/or prize recipients. Participation in these contests and sweepstakes is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. There are two situations in which SkyAuction.com will divulge this information to a third party provided the user gives express consent: (1) A user may expressly choose to receive additional information from the contest sponsor, in which case the user's personally identifiable information is divulged to the advertiser; (2) Some of the contests may be hosted on the SkyAuction.com site but administered by the sponsor; in such cases, the information a user provides is passed on to the third party as long as that user gives express consent. Because the rules and terms of each contest and sweepstakes can vary, all information about each contest and sweepstakes is clearly posted during the event. 

SURVEYS 

Occasionally SkyAuction.com conducts user surveys to better target our content to our audience. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any personally identifiable information with such third parties. 

LINKS TO OTHER SITES 

Users should be aware that when you are on SkyAuction.com, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from SkyAuction.com pages that take you outside our service. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement or a SkyAuction.com more information link, the click takes you off the SkyAuction.com site. This includes, but is not limited to, links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use SkyAuction.com's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. 

SkyAuction.com's policy does not extend to such third parties' use of such information, anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond SkyAuction.com's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

SECURITY 

SkyAuction.com has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our guests is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, SkyAuction.com can not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. SSL is a coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble data before you send it to us.

Unfortunately, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Therefore, although we will endeavor to protect your privacy as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private.

Your SkyAuction.com account is password protected so that only you can access it and view the member information relevant to the account. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. SkyAuction.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. 

YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the SkyAuction.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the SkyAuction.com Web site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting to the SkyAuction.com Web site.

CONTACTING THE WEB SITE 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact SkyAuction Customer Support via email or write to:   
SkyAuction.com   
Attn:Internet Development   
501 Madison Avenue   
New York, NY 10022

Last Updated Feb. 21, 2002
